So from here, once you have the feet and the legs aligned, same thing as the standing pose, you will move the left hip forward and the right hip back, pressing into the rear heel.
Keep the forward knee right over the ankle.
Notice the support you have the support of the chair, but also notice the support as you press into your legs.
Notice the flexibility this is bringing into your hips and your shoulders as you come up into your version of supported verbadrasana 1.
Either temple pose or "V" for victory pose.
Shoulders move down and back, crown lifts, the chin is leveled.
All the energy is coming right on up the inhale and you can drop down a little more on the exhale.
Really rely on the support of the chair here, even though you feel your feet and your legs supporting you.
Let the chair support you, particularly if you have knee injuries or hip issues.
That's what this is for.